<AppUpdater>
  <update>
    <latestVersion>5.6.2</latestVersion>
    <url>https://github.com/steve1316/uma-android-automation/releases</url>
    <releaseNotes>
v5.6.2 - Changelog

New
---
- Add `Trackblazer Item Conservation` section under the `Scenario Overrides Settings` page with thresholds for `Energy Item Reserve`, `Cupcake Reserve`, `Master Hammer Finale Reserve`, `Artisan Hammer Min Stock for G2 / G3`, `Glow Stick Final Reserve`, and `Glow Stick Min Fans`.
- Add `Prioritize Near-Max Friendship` toggle to the `Training Settings` page that applies an anticipatory rainbow multiplier in Year 2+ when a training has green/blue friendship bars near orange.
- Add `Training Level Weighting` toggle to the `Training Settings` page that detects each facility's training level (1-5) via OCR and amplifies the top three priority stats' scores accordingly.
- Add `Disable Per-Distance Stat Targets` toggle to the `Training Settings` page that treats every stat's target as the scenario stat cap.
- Add long-press on option labels across the settings pages to copy the option name to the clipboard.
- Add Android ripple feedback to `Button`, `Select`, `AlertDialog`, `CustomCheckbox`, `CustomSelect`, and `CustomSlider` press surfaces.
- Add `Decision Tracer` instrumentation that emits a structured `Decision Report` block at the end of every main-screen turn, summarizing trainee state, decision-relevant settings, the chosen action, rejected alternatives, training selection, and item usage.

Adjustments
---
- Upgrade to `Expo SDK 56` and `React Native 0.85`, replace the deprecated `@expo/vector-icons` with `@react-native-vector-icons/ionicons`, and migrate to the new `expo-file-system` `File` and `Paths` API.
- Gate `Trackblazer` race item conservation logic so it only kicks in from Turn 65 onward (right after Senior Year Summer training). Before that, the bot uses Hammers and Glow Sticks freely.
- Ensure that `Royal Kale Juice` with a `Berry Sweet Cupcake` or `Plain Cupcake` in the same inventory can rescan again to use the cupcake after queuing the Kale Juice when you are already at GREAT mood.
- Suppress the legacy extra-race fan-farming fallback when `Smart Race Solver` is enabled so the bot does not enter a race the solver did not plan.
- Let `Smart Race Solver` override `Trackblazer`'s grade filter for `Pre-OP` races so a solver-planned Pre-OP race can actually execute.
- Rest at critical energy with 3+ consecutive races even when a `Good-Luck Charm` is in inventory - the Charm only fires after `analyzeTrainings()` produces a selection with measured failure chance >= 20%, so it cannot protect the analysis itself.
- Rename `Trackblazer Charm` and `Trackblazer Item Floor` settings to behavior-first names in the `Scenario Overrides Settings` page for clarity.
- Group `Decision Report` inventory by category (Megaphones, Hammers, Energy, Cupcakes, etc.) and include `Trackblazer` race items.

Fixes
---
- Fix bug where per-distance strategy was falling back to the blanket strategy on mandatory races.
- Fix bug where `Smart Race Solver` ignored manual race locks at runtime and that locked races are not bundled into the schedule regeneration after a race loss.

    </releaseNotes>
  </update>
</AppUpdater>